The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Interesting !
A mere mortal
was able to remain conscious under my Divine Sense ?
Who
are you ?
No wonder you didn't pass out.
So that's how it is...
You
are not alone.
A top-grade puppet at the Illusory Yin realm !
I didn't expect to find
such a pleasant surprise on this trip.
Once I search your soul,
I will find
whoever made this puppet.
Stop !
Dad ?
This man is definitely not a second-step cultivator.
But why can't I see through his cultivation ?
A Thunder Celestial Messenger...
Who are you ?
Trying to run ?
Wilderness
Planet Ran Yun
Leave this puppet behind
and I will spare the three of you !
I'm the one
who won't spare you today.
If I arrived a second later,
you would've already killed my son.
No matter who you are,
you will
die today !
You overestimate yourself !
Even if
you have a puppet by your side,
do you think you can challenge a Thunder Celestial Messenger ?
Go !
This bit of thunder energy
is too weak !
A thunder spell ?
You...
You're Xu Mu !?
This
is true thunder !
You...
What the hell is your cultivation level !?
My cultivation level...
This is
his domain ?
His energy is still rising ?
Such a powerful domain...
This man is no ordinary cultivator.
If his domain has already reached the second step,
I'll have trouble beating him.
My mind has been particularly agitated today.
Dad,
will I understand today
why you didn't let me cultivate ?
No matter what happens,
I am by your side.
I didn't even realize that my domain
Life and Death Domain
Peak Late stage Ascendant
has reached Peak Late stage.
Fortunately,
his domain has not yet broken through the first step.
If his domain were in the second step
Wang Lin's avatar
Middle stage Ascendant
along with the puppet,
things wouldn't have ended well for me.
With such a low cultivation,
you dare to impersonate a Thunder Celestial Messenger !?
I will now,
show you what that title
really means !
Celestial Thunder Beast !
Only by possessing such a Thunder Beast,
can one be worthy of being called a Thunder Celestial Messenger !
Because of your crime,
your entire family shall be exterminated !
It hasn't even grown a horn
and you call that a Thunder Beast ?
A silver-horned Thunder Beast !?
It's really a sacred beast !
Even within the Thunder Celestial Temple,
only core messengers possess silver-horned sacred beasts...
For it to have fallen into the hands of a rogue cultivator like this
is such a waste !
If I kill this man,
this sacred beast will be mine !
Thunder Celestial Tribulation,
fall !
No thunder under the heavens
can harm me in the slightest.
This thunder
is no exception.
This was a spell bestowed by the Thunder Celestial Temple !
How did he break it so easily ?
A full power strike from a celestial artifact
still couldn't shake his foundation.
An Illusory Yin cultivator
is indeed formidable.
Your comprehension of the Thunder Dao
is indeed superior to mine.
If our cultivations were equal,
I would almost certainly have died.
What a pity, what a pity...
In the end, you're just an Ascendant cultivator.
Don't you know
that no matter how strong the spells of the first step are,
they're just mere spells.
While the origin energy of second step cultivators
touches the very essence of laws !
Hand over the silver-horned Thunder Beast and the puppet.
Otherwise,
I'll use my origin energy
to turn you all to ashes !
If you want to fight, then fight !
I have very little origin energy left.
If I consume more,
I'll be even further away from Corporeal Yang.
Given Xu Mu's talent,
he willingly lived in seclusion
and gifted a puppet to protect his son ?
Why don't
I find a flaw in his domain
and attack his heart ?
Why are you so nervous ?
I just want to know
if this mortal is aware
that he is already dead.
Silence !
The flaw in his domain
is indeed this mortal !
Since his physical body no longer exists,
why did you use a spell
to forcibly lock his soul here ?
Shut up !
Nice technique !
But it won't stop me !
Let me see
the secrets of your heaven defying
soul binding spell !
This...
This is...
Nirvana Cleanser sword energy !?
A madman...
He's a complete madman !
He used this kind of sword energy
to form flesh for a mere soul fragment !
If that sword energy had been aimed at me just now...
Die !
An origin energy spell !?
How...
How can he use an origin energy spell !?
You forced me to use my source origin energy !
Origin Energy
Thunder Cauldron
Origin Energy Thunder Cauldron !
Xu Mu,
let us see which one of us will survive
between you and me
in my Thunder Cauldron !
Refine !
What is he doing ?
Those runes...
why am I scared of them ?
God Slaying Chariot,
third seal,
open !
Im...
Impossible !
What kind of Thunder Beast is this !?
Heavenly...
Chop !
No...
Dad,
is what he said
true ?
If I cultivate,
my soul will be destroyed.
Is that right ?
My body
was formed from sword energy.
I...
have already died long ago...
You're not dead.
You
are who you are.
Dad,
you once taught me
to climb mountains when I encounter them,
to cross the rivers when I encounter them.
That if the heavens and the earth are in the way,
I must never give in.
Actually...
I already had the answer deep in my heart.
I just didn't dare to face it.
Why can't I cultivate ?
Why can't I have children ?
Why have I never been ill
during those 70 years ?
Why have I
never truly felt tired in my life ?
Now,
I understand everything.
No wonder I always
dreamed during my childhood
that I was in a world of golden light.
I, Wang Ping,
have no mother.
But fortunately, in this life,
I had you
and Qing Yi.
Dad,
you hid it from me for 70 years
just to give me a fulfilling life.
Thank you.
If there is a next life,
I will come looking for you.
Wang Ping...
It seems
I don't even have real tears to shed.
Dad,
take care.
Ping'er can't fulfill his promise
to accompany you through life forever.
Ping'er,
drink your medicine.
Dad,
the medicine is very bitter.
the medicine
is very bitter.
Dad,
Wang Ping and I made a promise
that I will accompany him even in the underworld.
I...
I want to stay with him !
You
won't regret it ?
I won't regret.
Dad,
take care.
Ping'er can't fulfill his promise
to accompany you through life forever.
Dad,
if I cultivate,
my soul will be destroyed.
Is that right ?
After I die,
send me to Father's side.
As for you, you will be free.
If I could choose,
and if there is a next life,
I wish to be with Father in a small mountain village secluded from the world.
We would live an ordinary,
peaceful life.
Dad...
Dad !
Father,
since you won't let me cultivate
then I will become
the supreme ruler among mortals !
Ping'er,
you've grown up.
The light in the clouds
pierces through the fog
without looking back.
There's no need to make a fuss,
let time
settle all grudges.
I will never forget how burning the tears of this world can be.
Don’t be afraid of gains and losses or the ups and downs of life.
When one has lived through the trials and tribulations of an ordinary life,
their heart remains unburdened as they look back on the passing years.
Looking back, the cycle of karma has always been there.
May you never be consumed by grudges and resentment in this life.
Take care,
Father.
I know you've seen all the world has to offer,
Spend a lifetime with Ping'er
but you’re still a child in my eyes.
and I'll give you Nascent Soul cultivation.
Are you willing ?
But I truly cannot understand
why Father refuses to let me cultivate !
I told you,
you're not suited for it.
That girl named Qing Yi
seems like a good person.
I don’t need you
to discipline my son.
Everything in this world
is born homeless
like the echoes of fate.
But the scent of the locust tree
brings back memories of home
as if you were right by my side.
Don’t ask me if it was fate or a trial, it will be impossible to forget.
Sun
Tai's
Grave
Don't ask me how long it will take for us to meet again.
Dad,
I will spend my life
accompanying you.
Even in death.
How can our relation be measured
by the number of days and nights we spent together ?
Let’s simply keep each other in our thoughts.
Looking back at the past, I have come to see through it all.
But upon my return, I still say I have no regrets for having poured out my heart.
There’s no need to dwell on the past,
it's enough that this memory remains in my heart for the rest of my life.
Ping'er can't lie to Dad.
I can't make Dad sad !
Dad...
The medicine is very bitter...
Let dust return to dust,
Looking back at the past, I have come to see through it all.
let dirt return to dirt.
Above the Life and Death reincarnation cycle
lies the elusive karma.
But upon my return, I still say I have no regrets for having poured out my heart.
The resentment you bear,
There’s no need to dwell on the past,
born from bloodshed,
must also be dissolved in the mortal world.
it's enough that this memory remains in my heart for the rest of my life.
This time,
I will grant you a new life.
Enter this world of human existence,
to truly live
the life you deserve.
Above Life and Death
there is...
Karma.